<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://blog.otohits.net</id>
    <title>Otohits blog</title>
    <updated>2023-08-27T15:17:20.376Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/webmasterish/vuepress-plugin-feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://blog.otohits.net"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://blog.otohits.net/feed.atom"/>
    <subtitle>News and articles about Otohits.net website. Stay up to date with the new features for your surf.</subtitle>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using the throttling to limit the visits]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.otohits.net/2023/08/15/using-throttling/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.otohits.net/2023/08/15/using-throttling/">
        </link>
        <updated>2023-08-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Throttling helps you control the number of visits you will receive per hour (and therefore, the number of points your link will use).

We recommend you use it on new links to test them to avoid wasting too many points.

There are 2 ways to use the throttling:

Using the classic limit per hour
 ...]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Link's templates]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.otohits.net/2023/08/14/links-templates/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.otohits.net/2023/08/14/links-templates/">
        </link>
        <updated>2023-08-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Templates help you quickly copy options on different links.

It can be very helpful especially with override options (referers, user-agents) as it will load the lists directly when you create a new link.

Here are the steps to create and use templates:

Choose a link as a base model to make the ...]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overriding the user-agent]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.otohits.net/2023/08/13/overriding-the-useragent/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.otohits.net/2023/08/13/overriding-the-useragent/">
        </link>
        <updated>2023-08-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[User-agent is like a signature of your browser. With the user-agent, a website knows which browser you are using.

Here is an example of a user-agent: Mozilla/5.0 (Windows NT 5.1; rv:31.0) Gecko/20100101 Firefox/31.0

The above example shows you the Firefox 31 user-agent.

You can check your cur ...]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to override the referer]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.otohits.net/2023/08/12/how-to-override-the-referer/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.otohits.net/2023/08/12/how-to-override-the-referer/">
        </link>
        <updated>2023-08-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The referrer identifies the webpage that the previous request comes from. If you need more explanations on this concept, you can referer to the guide about hiding the referer.

When you override the referer, you make the page believe that the visit comes ...]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to hide the referer]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.otohits.net/2023/08/11/how-to-hide-the-referer/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.otohits.net/2023/08/11/how-to-hide-the-referer/">
        </link>
        <updated>2023-08-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The referrer identifies the webpage that the previous request comes from. As an example, if I go to google to look for something, then I click on the result http://mysite.com, mysite.com will be able to know that I come from google.

You can test it yourself: go to [https://anonymiz.com/myrefe ...]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use clicks]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.otohits.net/2023/08/10/how-to-use-clicks/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.otohits.net/2023/08/10/how-to-use-clicks/">
        </link>
        <updated>2023-08-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Clicks is one of the most powerful features available on Otohits. It helps you set up a "real" navigation on your website.

To use it correctly, there are few things to know that we will talk about in this article.

Making sure your link is compatible

Clicks feature does not work on every webs ...]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[App update, Docker App official support, indirect MacOs availability]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.otohits.net/2020/10/21/docker-support/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.otohits.net/2020/10/21/docker-support/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-10-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are the main changes introduced between versions 5063 and 5066.

Fixed bugs

Desktop App only: on some occasion, the application could hang and take at most 5 minutes to continue surfing. It will now continue as fast as usual (30 seconds max if the viewer does not respond).
Desktop Ap ...]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Efficiency system update]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.otohits.net/2020/10/03/efficiency-system-update/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.otohits.net/2020/10/03/efficiency-system-update/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-10-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Otohits was created, the ratio was 1:1, meaning that for each second you visit a website, you earned 1 point. To keep a balance on the platform and avoid inflation (points value decrease), some basic modifiers were introduced to make this ratio varies. The chosen name to express this ratio ...]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[App v5 update: refined locales, points report and new parameter]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.otohits.net/2020/09/20/app-v5-update-5063/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.otohits.net/2020/09/20/app-v5-update-5063/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-09-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Applicable to v5063 and upper

Locales now match the country of the App

App v5 came with a basic locale (language) support. It was taken from the current operating system settings and in a lot of scenarios would have still resulted in an en-US locale.

With the recent upgrade of [geotargetin ...]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Geotargeting udpate: a complete redesign]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.otohits.net/2020/08/31/geotargeting-update-complete-redesign/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.otohits.net/2020/08/31/geotargeting-update-complete-redesign/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-08-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Geotargeting appeared 4 years ago on Otohits. Since then, it never got any major update. The list of available countries was based on how much visits were generated by locations.
From time to time, we updated the list, but you were a lot asking for additional countries to be added.

In the end, it ...]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v5 update - Windows 32 Bits support and User-Agent update]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.otohits.net/2020/06/30/v5-version-5055-32-bits-platform/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.otohits.net/2020/06/30/v5-version-5055-32-bits-platform/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-06-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the last post of the v5 release as well as the removal of the v3/Definitive edition of the App page, some of you contacted us regarding the lack of a 32 Bits version for the Windows App.

We didn't think there was st ...]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v5 App: official release]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.otohits.net/2020/06/27/v5-app-update/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.otohits.net/2020/06/27/v5-app-update/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-06-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the launch of the v5 App 2 months ago, it is now the most used version of the App.
I want to thank everyone, whether you just used it or helped us to make it better as you were encountering abnormal behavior.

Over these last 2 months, 32 updates have be ...]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New feature: Page reload]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.otohits.net/2020/05/30/new-feature-reload-page/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.otohits.net/2020/05/30/new-feature-reload-page/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-05-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Page reload is the first new feature that has been implemented in the new v5 application. When activated on your links, it will simply "reload" the current page.

This feature is marked as experimental for the moment due to the fact that there are still so ...]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applications - v5 is out]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.otohits.net/2020/04/26/application-v5/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.otohits.net/2020/04/26/application-v5/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-04-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything is explained in the previous article. As a short explanation, old Apps were really hard to maintain and to add features in. The v5 has been designed to be flexible and easier to upgrade.

Highlights
The v5 is now available as a console app for both ...]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applications: the old (v3), the current (definitive) and the next one]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.otohits.net/2020/03/21/app-old-and-new/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.otohits.net/2020/03/21/app-old-and-new/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-03-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The v3 of the App was launched in August 2015 on Windows. The .Net Framework was not necessary anymore, but it was a simple window without the possibility to see the navigated websites.

App v3.1 for Windows

Quickly after, the 3.1 came out to bring back this fe ...]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Otohits blog]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.otohits.net/2020/03/09/first-news/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.otohits.net/2020/03/09/first-news/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-03-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the beginning of Otohits, newsletters were the only way of communicating with you. Although it was perfect few years ago, it became more and more complicated to use.

From newsletters to blog posts

The last newsletter was sent more than 2 years ago (November 2017). It doesn't mean that wor ...]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newsletter - Definitive Edition App]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.otohits.net/2017/11/05/newsletter-definitive-edition/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.otohits.net/2017/11/05/newsletter-definitive-edition/">
        </link>
        <updated>2017-11-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a copy of an old Othits newsletter

Coin miners are spreading over a lot of websites. We consider them to be clearly not adapted to autosurfs as they are mostly misused (taking up all the CPU without user consent). It will likely result in a bad user experience and as such we do not approv ...]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newsletter - Happy birthday Otohits!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.otohits.net/2017/05/25/newsletter-anniversary-4/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.otohits.net/2017/05/25/newsletter-anniversary-4/">
        </link>
        <updated>2017-05-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a copy of an old Othits newsletter

Otohits is 4 years old!
Let's take a moment to see what happened during this year.

We welcomed 49 000 new members as well as providing almost 7 billion visits, that's more than the 3 previous years combined!
To all the members: a big thanks for all of y ...]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newsletter - High quality mod]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.otohits.net/2017/03/04/newsletter-high-quality/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.otohits.net/2017/03/04/newsletter-high-quality/">
        </link>
        <updated>2017-03-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a copy of an old Othits newsletter

A new feature will be released soon, it's called the "High quality mod".
The concept is quite simple: activating this feature will considerably reduce the visits from proxies/VPS/Servers and low quality computers and thus provide a more natural traffic f ...]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newsletter - Otohits Api]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.otohits.net/2016/11/30/otohits-api/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.otohits.net/2016/11/30/otohits-api/">
        </link>
        <updated>2016-11-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a copy of an old Othits newsletter

We are happy to push forward the autosurf world by providing you the Otohits API. Officially launched today, it is a brand new way to use and manage your links and data, but also a new tool that allows you to imagine, create and share new solutions for a ...]]></summary>
    </entry>
</feed>